<faq>
	<section name="Auto Updates">
		<question id="updatesgray">
			<q>
				Automatic updates are grayed out for me, how come?
			</q>
			<a>
				Automatic updates in 5.4 through to at least 5.8 have been disabled in Vista / Windows 7, as they require
				administrative privileges.  Hopefully a fix will appear soon, to start a UAC prompt on these OSes if the user has
				admin privileges.
			</a>
		</question>
		
		<question id="updatesdelay">
			<q>
				I see from the website there's a new version, but I haven't got a notification to update yet. 
				Even if I click "Update Notepad++" it doesn't update, what's going on?
			</q>
			<a>
				 The file that says what version is "current", lies on the website, and is manually updated.  
				 This update is done, when the release is considered stable enough - that can take any amount of time, 
				 depending on how stable the first release in a line is.  
				 There was a change in the gup.exe around the time 5.4 due to a change in the way SF downloads works, 
				 so versions prior to that will not auto-update.
			</a>
		</question>
		
	
	</section>
	
	<section name="Portability">
		<question id="linux">
			<q>
				I really like Notepad++, but I use Linux/Mac OS X/another OS - have you any plans to port it?
			</q>
			<a>
				
			</a>
		</question>
	</section>
	
	<section name="Editing">
		<question id="marklines">
			<q>
				I want to extract all the lines that contain a certain string (or regular expression), how do i do that?
			</q>
			<a>
				
			</a>
		</question>
	</section>
	
	
	<section name="Syntax Highlighting">
		<question id="syntax">
			<q>
				I noticed there's no option for language Foo/Bar/WhizBang.  Any plans on adding it?
			</q>
			<a>
				Scintilla, externals lexers, UDLs
			</a>
		</question>
		<question id="extendinglang">
			<q>
				I want to make some modifications to the way XX language is highlighted, how can I change it?
			</q>
			<a>
				Keywords, scintilla lexers, recompiling (wiki link)
			</a>
		</question>
	</section>
	
	<section name="User Defined Languages">
		<question id="udl">
			<q>
				Folding issue
			</q>
			<a>
				
			</a>
		</question>
	</section>
	
	<section name="Plugins">
		<question id="plugins">
			<q>
				Where can I find plugins for Notepad++?
			</q>
			<a>
				TODO: Plugin Manager, Plugin Central
			</a>
		</question>
	</section>
	
	<section name="Problems and Errors">
		<question id="langsxml">
			<q>
				I get a message about Langs.xml could not be loaded at startup, what's wrong?
			</q>
			<a>
				
			</a>
		</question>
		
		<question id="crash">
			<q>
				Notepad++ just crashed on me, can I get my documents back?
			</q>
			<a>
				
			</a>
		</question>
		
		<question id="bugs">
			<q>
				I think I've found a bug in Notepad++, what should I do?
			</q>
			<a>
				Plugins, reporting, bug tracker
			</a>
		</question>
	</section>
	
	<section name="Configuration">
		<question id="config">
			<q>
				Where are Notepad++ configuration files kept?
			</q>
			<a>
				
			</a>
		</question>
		
	</section>
	
	<section name="Help and Suggestions">
		<question id="help">
			<q>
				I want to do something in Notepad++ that I'm sure should be possible, where's the best place to ask?
			</q>
			<a>
				Search the wiki (TODO: link).   If not, the Help forum.  TODO: Link
			</a>
		</question>
		<question id="ideas">
			<q>
				I've got a suggestion for a feature / improvement.  Where should I suggest it?
			</q>
			<a>
				TODO: Link for Idea Torrent.
			</a>
		</question>

		<question id="faq">
			<q>
				Someone's asked a question on a forum that's answered in this FAQ, should I reprimand them?
			</q>
			<a>
				No. Just respond with a link to the FAQ entry that answers the question.  That way when people search
				the forums, or Google, they get a link to the answer.
			</a>
		</question>
</faq>